<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>BAISI HAIR - BLOGS</title>
  <updated>2020-10-13T11:21:27+08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>BAISI HAIR</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/wig-cap-construction</id>
    <published>2020-10-13T11:21:27+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:27+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/wig-cap-construction"/>
    <title>Wig Cap Construction</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Many people think that the main difference between wigs is the style. That is a big point of difference, but there’s another very important element to consider—the wig cap construction.<br>Wig hair is attached to the cap via different methods and constructions. Each has its own advantages you should consider before purchasing.<br>This is where we see why some wigs are significantly more expensive than others. Don’t automatically reject a wig because it’s a lot more expensive than other options.<br>You will get what you pay for.<br>You may end up paying more for your wig, but you should also expect a longer life from your wig as well as a more natural look.<br>Take a look at these primary differences between wig cap constructions for help deciding which type will best serve your personal needs.</p>
<p><strong>100% Hand-Tied Wig</strong></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/1_08c3703d-0be1-4105-b6c7-af85942a3d9b.jpg?v=1602558564" alt=""></p>
<p>100% hand-tied wig is also known as a hand-knotted wig. This type of wig offers what many consider to be the most natural appearance since the wig hair moves so freely.<br>You can look forward to freely and naturally moving hair, since every single hair on these types of wigs is tied by hand to the base.<br>These are the best types for those of you with sensitive scalps or hair loss since they are the softest and most comfortable cap.<br>You’ll enjoy fantastic versatility when it comes to styling since you’ll be able to comb your hair in virtually any direction.<br>It features the lightest type of construction method, which makes it ideal for wearing all day every day!</p>
<a style="display:none;" href="https://www.diamondpaintingplus.com">Diamond Painting</a>
<p><strong>Lace Front Wig</strong></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/2_a082fe96-de59-40b6-8dc1-a7fc6d99d948.jpg?v=1602558583" alt=""></p>
<p>If you’re looking for an incredibly natural hairline, then this is an ideal type for you.<br>Choose this type of wig if you frequently style your hair away from your face.<br>Every hair is tied by hand to the sheer lace section, but not to the whole cap. The material is also more delicate than other types of wig cap constructions, so you’ll need to be careful when handling. This also means it’s not a good choice if you live a very active lifestyle.<br>Many of these lace-front wigs come to you ready to wear and cover your head from one temple to the other.</p>
<p><strong>Monofilament Top Wig</strong></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/3_811711d2-be62-44f9-a460-4e33b9ac2992.jpg?v=1602558604" alt=""></p>
<p>The monofilament wig cap makes it look like there is natural hair growing from the scalp at the site of the part.<br>In this type of wig cap construction, individual hand tying is used for the sheer base but not the entire cap. But, you can wear this wig with ultra confidence since it does such a good job of making it look like natural growth emanating from your scalp where the hair is parted.<br>Do you want extra comfort?<br>The double mono layer of extra soft material can do that for you. You can choose from full top, parting, or crown areas.<br>If you simply can’t decide which wig to buy, you can’t go wrong with a monofilament top wig since it’s considered to be the most popular type of wig.</p>
<p><strong>Open Cap / Wefted Wig</strong></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/4_3491613d-3726-4df5-8848-389984d7e199.jpg?v=1602558625" alt=""></p>
<p>This type of wig construction is the most basic. It gives you instant lift thanks to the pre-teasing at the roots.<br>If budget is a primary concern, this type of construction will give you the most bang for your buck. And they’re very durable, helping you get even more for your money.<br>You’re sure to love how cool your scalp feels since this type offers excellent air ventilation from the open-weft construction.<br>Flexible options include capless and other traditional types.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/the-ultimate-first-time-wig-buyers-guide-how-to-choose-your-first-wig</id>
    <published>2020-10-13T10:48:03+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:29+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/the-ultimate-first-time-wig-buyers-guide-how-to-choose-your-first-wig"/>
    <title>How to Choose Your First Wig</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong>The 5 Factors to Buying the Right Wig So That You Love the Way You Look and Feel</strong></p>
<p>Are you buying a wig for the first time?<br>It can seem a little daunting.<br>But, did you know...<br>Millions of people wear wigs every day—you’re definitely not alone.<br>It’s quite possible that even your neighbors and colleagues wear wigs and you have no idea!<br>That’s because today’s wigs look more natural and beautiful than ever before.<br>In fact, today’s top celebrities not only wear wigs on the red carpet and in movies, but also in everyday life, too.<br>And even if this isn’t your first wig, you may learn some new tips that will assist you in choosing your next wig.<br>Here are the 5 factors that go into finding the perfect wig to achieve a more beautiful you:</p>
<ul>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Hairstyle</span></li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Length</span></li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Texture</span></li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Color</span></li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cap Size</span></li>
</ul>
<p>Let’s dive in!</p>
<p><strong>What Style Wig Should I Choose?</strong></p>
<p>We get it...<br>There are hundreds (in not thousands) of different wig styles to choose from.<br>And if it’s going to be your first time wearing a wig, you might feel a little timid about the whole experience, but rest assured, there’s no need to be scared!<br>Wigs have improved significantly over the years and now offer the exact look you desire, seamlessly integrating with your scalp and facial features.<br>For your first wig, you should consider wearing something that more closely matches your current or previous hairstyle.<br>Staying with what you’re familiar with will make the ongoing maintenance and styling of your hair easier.<br>Many wigs can be styled to look differently, so you can always look into taking your wig to a salon that specializes in wig care or doing it yourself at a later time.</p>
<a style="display: none;" href="https://www.korynhair.com/">Koryn Hair</a>
<p><strong>Length</strong><br>There are 3 main lengths to choose from:</p>
<ul>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Short wigs</span></li>
</ul>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/2132.jpg?v=1602557653" alt=""></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Medium length wigs</span></li>
</ul>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/213.jpg?v=1602556880" alt=""></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Long wigs</span></li>
</ul>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/1231.jpg?v=1602556937" alt=""><br>Short wigs are admittedly better for more humid areas or if you feel that your body is always hot. The longer the wig (just like the longer your hair) the more heat will be trapped and the warmer you might feel throughout the day. Also, short wigs are a bit easier to maintain, dry faster, are quicker to style, and can cost less.</p>
<p>But the choice is yours, don’t let money get in the way of achieving the look you want.</p>
<p><strong>Texture</strong><br>Once you know your desired length, you have a few choices for your desired texture:<br><strong>Straight:</strong> Straight and flat.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/15414.jpg?v=1602556986" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Wavy:</strong> Flowing and bouncy, but not curled.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/234154.jpg?v=1602557015" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Curly:</strong> Heat-Friendly and pops back like a slinky.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/6431.jpg?v=1602557515" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>What Shape Is Your Face?</strong><br>When selecting your wig style, it’s not your personal preference that should be the main consideration.<br>Instead, you should carefully consider what type of wig style looks best with your face shape.<br>Even though you may prefer a certain wig style, the most important thing to keep in mind is which wig will best flatter the shape of your head and face.<br>This will help you determine the length, texture, and overall style of wig to choose.<br>Here are the different face shapes and the styles that look best with each one:</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/12123.jpg?v=1602554580" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>Oval-Shaped Face</strong><br>If your face is balanced and evenly proportioned, you can wear almost any style. Off the face wigs will serve you best.<br>You should avoid wigs that feature heavy bangs or significant forward direction, which can create the perception of more weight in your face.<br><strong>Round-Shaped Face</strong><br>Your best choices are styles that succeed in adding fullness as well as height at the crown of your head.<br>These wig styles include off-center parts.<br>You would do well to wear shorter wigs that feature a swept-back direction or those with lengths that go past your chin.<br>You should avoid chin-length hair with a rounded line that closely matches your face's circular shape, center parts, very short cropped styles and fullness at the sides of the ears.<br>If you wear a rounded wig that doesn’t go past your chin, it will probably make the widest part of your face look fuller and wider.<br><strong>Square-Shaped Face</strong><br>Your best choices for this shape of face include wigs that are short to medium in length. You should look especially beautiful in those with waves or roundness around the face.<br>Be sure to consider wigs with wispy bangs, off-center parts, and those that provide height at the crown of your head. Layers and wispy looks succeed in softening your naturally square face.<br>With more height provided by your wig at the crown of your head, you will elongate your symmetrical face shape. <br>You’ll look lovely with curls or waves as those will balance your straight and symmetrical features. You should avoid straight bangs with linear lines, center parts, as well as styles that are long and straight.<br>This includes avoiding straight bobs that end at your jawline. If your wig does not go below your jawline, then you can also wear a layered bob.<br><strong>Oblong or Rectangular-Shaped Face</strong><br>Your best choices include short or medium-length wig styles since these can minimize the length of your face.<br>For example, you probably shouldn’t choose a wig that goes past your shoulders.<br>If you want to soften the straight lines of your face, then you should look for wigs with layers. If you want to minimize the geometric appearance of your face, wigs with side parts can help you with that. <br>You can shorten the appearance of your longer face with soft and wispy-banged wigs.<br>If you would like to add width to the appearance of your face, then look for wigs that offer fullness at the sides.<br>You should avoid longer or taller wig styles since these will further elongate the look of your facial features. You should also consider avoiding wigs with center parts.<br><strong>Heart-Shaped Face</strong><br>Your best choices are chin-length or longer wig styles, including hair that’s parted to the side, swept forward in layers around the upper part of your face, and even gently wispy bangs.</p>
<p><strong>Heart-Shaped Face</strong><br>Your best choices are chin-length or longer wig styles, including hair that’s parted to the side, swept forward in layers around the upper part of your face, and even gently wispy bangs.<br>A chin-length bob may be perfect for you since it creates a balanced look by giving fullness in all the right places. <br>Shorter wig styles can suit you. But it should be noted that if you have a very intense heart-shaped face, you’ll do best with a wig style that succeeds in adding weight in the back nape area of your neck.<br>This will allow you to enjoy beautiful balance between your pronounced cheekbones and narrow chin. You should avoid short, full styles with tapered necklines since these tend to put more attention on the upper part of your face, which can make you look unevenly distributed or top heavy.<br>If the wig creates the look of too much weight at the crown, it will make your face look longer with an even narrower chin.<br><strong>Diamond-Shaped Face</strong><br>With this shape of face, your best choices are actually just about any style you desire since the balanced shape of your face will be flattered by most any wig.<br>You’re lucky to be able to try a variety of wig styles!<br>It should be noted thought that if your face is more of a dramatic shape and you are more interested in a short wig style, you should consider wigs that provide more weight in the nape area.<br>Wearing these types will help you maintain a balanced look between your dramatic cheekbones and delicate chin. The only types of wigs you might consider avoiding are those with a lot of hair since they’ll probably hide your wonderful facial features.<br><a style="display: none;" href="https://www.wholesaleminkhairvendors.com/">Wholesale Hair</a><strong>Pear-Shaped Face</strong><br>The best choices for this type of face are wig styles that promote the appearance of width at your forehead and temples.<br>This will help create the illusion of a more oval face, drawing people’s attention to the upper part of your face.<br>The wig hair should be styled closer to your head on the sites and at the nape, to minimize the width at the jawline area of your face. You should think about avoiding full and long wig styles that would put more focus on your jawline.<br>How Your Daily Lifestyle Effects Your Wig Choice<br>Are you typically at a desk inside for most of the day? Or do you live a very <strong>active life that includes sports?</strong><br>If most of your day is spent inside at a desk, then you may want to select synthetic wigs or heat-friendly synthetic wigs. They are less durable than human hair wigs, but you can take advantage of a smaller price tag since you won’t be demanding as much from your wig.<br>On the other hand, if you’re typically more active, human hair as well as premium human and Remy hair hybrid wigs will likely serve you better since they are the most durable.<br><strong>What Look Are You Going For?</strong><br>Aside from durability, you’ll also want to think about the type of look you’ll most frequently wear.<br>If you work in an office every day, you’ll obviously want to consider a wig that will help you achieve a professional look.<br>Therefore, consider shorter length wigs.<br>If you want to achieve a look that’s more on the cute side, then consider getting a pre-styled wig that features curls.<br>This brings up an important consideration: Curling your own wig can be tricky, since you shouldn’t apply high-temperature heat to most wigs because it can actually melt the hairs.<br>You can buy heat-friendly synthetic wigs, which typically allow you to apply up to 350 degrees of heat while styling.<br>But if you think you’ll want cute curls just about every day, then you might as well buy a wig that comes with permanent curls.<br>It’s easy to get caught up in all the sexy, fun, and glamorous wig styles, but you should stick with what will best suit your daily needs.<br>Once you’ve gotten your first wig for daily wear, you can always come back and look for a wig that you’ll love wearing for costumes or special occasions.<br>Since it’s completely common for people to frequently dye and restyle their hair, it won’t seem awkward if your hair looks completely different from time to time.<br>The only thing that will stand out is your luxurious new looks!<br>If you’re still having difficulty narrowing down your choices, consider starting with the following primary categories of wigs and working your way through the options:</p>
<ul>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Short wigs</span></li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Medium length wigs</span></li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Long wigs</span></li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Special Occasion wigs</span></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Choosing the Perfect Wig Hair Color</strong></p>
<div style="text-align: left;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/513_600x600.jpg?v=1602558111" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<p>There is no shortage of variation in wig colors, however, finding the exact color to match you or your original hair color can be a very tricky task...<br>If this is your first wig, you may want to consider remaining closer to your natural hair color. You can always try new, different colors later.<br>It’s also important to keep your natural skin tone in mind when selecting your wig color.<br>Look for wig colors that will best compliment your natural skin tone, which isn’t necessarily going to be your favorite color of wig.<br><strong>Variations Between Wig Brands</strong><br>Finding the right color is the riskiest part of buying a new wig, so be sure to spend a few extra minutes matching up to your desired color.<br>Each wig brand is likely to have a slightly different color labeling system, which means moving between brands can be a bit tricky.<br>The most important thing is to remember the exact color name for your favorite styles so that you can get an exact replacement when your old wig inevitably deteriorates.<br><strong>What Cap Size Do I Need?</strong><br>The size of the wig can make an even bigger difference than the actual style since it’s directly related to your comfort.<br>If you get it too small, it won’t fit on your head.<br>If it’s too big, it might be obvious you’re wearing a wig.<br>95% of wig wearers are actually classified as average size. But, you can easily find wigs that come in petite and large sizes as well.<br>But, how do you figure out if you’re average size or not?<br><strong>How to Find Your Wig Cap Size</strong></p>
<p><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/12154.jpg?v=1602558169" alt=""></strong></p>
<p>If you’re not sure about what size of cap you should choose, you will need to use a tailoring measuring tape to measure the circumference of your head.<br>Measure from the front of your hairline, behind your ear, to the nape of your neck, to your other ear, and then match the measuring tape back to the other end at the front of your hairline.<br><strong>Pro Tip:</strong> To make sure your measurement is accurate, try measuring at least three times to make sure your number is consistent.<br>Now, all you need to do is match your measurement to one in the list below.<br>Standard Circumference Sizes:<br><strong>19 inches:</strong> child<br><strong>21 inches:</strong> petite<br><strong>21.5 inches:</strong> petite/average<br><strong>22 inches:</strong> average<br><strong>22.5 inches:</strong> average/large<br><strong>23 inches:</strong> large<br><strong>Note:</strong> If you use a different wig size chart than the one provided here, be sure the size chart you’re looking at online is for circumference since that’s what you’ll have measured if you used the above tip. For example, some size charts offer ear-to-ear sizes, not circumference.<br><strong>Wig Straps</strong><br>What makes wig sizing even more convenient is that most come with some type of strap, commonly Velcro, which allow you to easily adjust the size of your wig for the best fit possible.<br>They usually allow you to adjust smaller or larger by a half inch.<br>Therefore, if you’re concerned your wig might be a little too small, you should still get the size that’s recommended according to the circumference of your head since you can adjust the size up.<br>It’s better to be slightly more snug than too loose.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/14-wig-wearing-tips-from-hair-experts</id>
    <published>2020-01-11T16:05:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:30+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/14-wig-wearing-tips-from-hair-experts"/>
    <title>14 Wig Wearing Tips from Hair Experts</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Wearing a wig can be a lot of fun whether you're doing it to cover hair loss or just want to enjoy the variety of hair styles, lengths and colors that wearing a wig makes it possible to achieve.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/14-wig-wearing-tips-from-hair-experts">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span>Wearing a wig can be a lot of fun whether you're doing it to cover hair loss or just want to enjoy the variety of hair styles, lengths and colors that wearing a wig makes it possible to achieve.this blog will help guide you along with some very simple tips on how you can wear these appearance-enhancing aids. For some people dressed in a wig can seem a bit daunting until you get comfortable with them. </span></p>
<p><span><strong>1.Be Confident</strong><br><br>The right attitude is key to pulling off any hairstyle. If you are constantly worrying or fidgeting with your wig it won't look good. Own it! Walk tall, be confident and you will be able to pull off any look you want.<br><br><strong>2.Customize Your Cut</strong><br><br>Take your wig to your hairstylist to have bangs cut or trimmed, shaped or thinned out to remove excess bulk. A custom cut can make a world of difference. Think of your wig like a designer suit. Sure, you can wear it off the rack and it can look good, but with a little tailoring it can look GREAT!<br><br> <strong>3.Invest in the Right Care Products</strong><br><br>If you want to extend the life of your wig and keep it looking beautiful the proper care products are essential.For human hair wigs, choose sulfate-free care products or products specifically formulated for color treated hair to keep the color looking vibrant, longer. <br><br> <a style="display: none;" href="https://www.korynhair.com/">Koryn Hair</a><strong>4.Always Think Ahead</strong><br><br>You should always have two wigs ready to wear at all times.This way you always have something to wear when you are washing your wig and a back up if anything should happen to one. Rotating between wigs also helps to extend the life.<br><br><strong>5.Kitchen Tips</strong><br><br>If you love to cook here is a tip every wig wearer should know; NEVER open the oven while wearing a synthetic wig! The sudden burst of heat will ruin your wig; even the hot steam from a boiling pot of water can cause irreparable damage.<br><br><strong>6.Personalize Your Look</strong><br><br>Add a headband, scarf or any hair accessory to create a personal touch. Just because you are wearing a wig doesn't mean you have to wear it the same way all the time. Be creative.<br><br><strong>7.Blend in your Own Hair</strong><br><br>If your natural hair is somewhat close to your wig color try blending in your own hair along the hairline for a more natural look. Apply the wig then pull out small sections of your own hair along the sides and front using your fingers or a rattail comb.<br><br><a style="display:none;" href="https://www.diamondpaintingplus.com">Diamond Painting</a><strong>8.Stay Close to your Current Style</strong><br><br>Choose a wig close to your current hairstyle. What is going to look the most natural on you, is a style that looks like YOU! A familiar style will help you feel more confident and make the transition from wearing your own hair to wearing wigs a good experience. Experiment with subtle style variations, but stay within your comfort zone.<br><br><strong>9.Don't Forget Styling Products</strong><br><br>Give your hair a salon finish and define layers using styling products (Shaping Cream or Style &amp; Hold Hair Spray works great on synthetic hair).<br><br><strong>10.Know Your Measurements</strong><br><br>There is nothing worse than an ill fit wig. You don't want your wig riding up, slipping off or to look misshapen by excess bulk at the crown. This is why choosing the right size is just as important as finding the right color and style.<br><br><strong>11.Create Different Hairstyles</strong><br><br>If your hair is chin length or longer, try a half-up, half-down style. For longer wigs, try a loose updo or low ponytail. <br><br>To make these looks work; keep it soft, loose and a little messy. Keep the bangs down (unless you have a lace front wig) and pull down a few tendrils of hair along the hairline to keep it looking natural.<br><br><strong>12.Go Curly or Straight</strong><br><br>A new generation of hair tools allow you to curl or straighten both human hair and synthetic hair! These revolutionary new tools have a special setting specifically for synthetic wigs, hairpieces <a style="display: none;" href="https://www.sheinhair.com/">Hair Extensions</a> so you can easily go curly to straight or straight to curly without damaging your wig. A must-have for any wig!<br><br><strong>13.Try a New Do</strong><br><br>Bored with the same hairstyle? baisi wigs follow current hair trends. As new hair fashions hit the scene, new wig styles become available. Trying a new wig style is an easy way to test drive current hair trends without any commitment, keep your look modern and beat hair boredom. Change up your look from day to day. Don't get suck in a rut. <br><br><strong>14.Don't Be Afraid of Color</strong><br><br>If you've found a wig you love and don't want to change your style, try a new color to freshen up your look. <br><br>Most people can wear up to three shades darker or lighter than their natural color. Also, don't be afraid to change your color for the season. It's not uncommon to go slightly lighter in the spring and summer and darker in the fall and winter. <br><br>baisi Hair wigs are extremely popular and the latest styles, they look natural as well. if you follow the wig wearing tips listed above, you'll love wearing them and the versatility they deliver. For more information, contact us directly.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/what-s-the-differences-of-5-5-wig-6-6-wig-13-4-wig-13-6-wig-frontal-lace-wig-360-wig-and-full-lace-wig</id>
    <published>2019-12-14T14:53:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:32+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/what-s-the-differences-of-5-5-wig-6-6-wig-13-4-wig-13-6-wig-frontal-lace-wig-360-wig-and-full-lace-wig"/>
    <title>What&apos;s the differences of wig</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>The difference of all of them is the size of the lace inside the wig.</p>
<p><strong>5*5 wig</strong> made by a 5x5 Lace Closure with bundles of hair, the lace size is 5*5.</p>
<p><strong>6*6 wig</strong> made by a 6x6 Lace Closure with bundles of hair, the lace size is 6*6.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/4.png?v=1576306310" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>13*4 wig </strong>made by a 13*4 Lace Frontal with bundles of hair, the lace size is 13*4.</p>
<p><strong>13*6 wig </strong>made by a 13*6 Lace Frontal with bundles of hair, the lace size is 13*6.</p>
<p>Both 13*4 wig and 13*6 wig called <strong>frontal lace wig.</strong></p>
<p><strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/5.png?v=1576306340" alt=""></strong></p>
<p><strong>360 lace wig</strong> made by a 360 frontal with bundles of hair, the lace size is 22.5*6*2inch</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/6_e7acb61e-3a32-4920-8413-c04e76b31477.jpg?v=1576306369" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>A full lace wig</strong> is constructed from a lace cap that covers the whole head and the 100% human hair is knotted into this by hand.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/7.jpg?v=1576306399" alt=""></p>
<p>The back look of frontal lace wig and full lace wig</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/8.jpg?v=1576306424" alt=""></p>
<p>Wholesale, Drop Shipping and Customized Hair Package,</p>
<p>Pls feel free to contact:</p>
<p>Tel/Whatsapp: +86 185 8876 9406 , Direct Link to Whatsapp <span><a href="https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406">https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406</a></span></p>
Email: <a href="mailto:luxy1@baisihair.com">luxy1@baisihair.com</a>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-measure-your-wig-length</id>
    <published>2019-12-14T14:48:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:33+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-measure-your-wig-length"/>
    <title>How to Measure Your Wig Length?</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>When you <strong>measuring</strong> your hair <strong>wig</strong>, for curly and wavy hair, it should be stretched to straight when you <strong>measure</strong> the hair <strong>length</strong>. <a style="display: none;" href="https://www.wholesaleminkhairvendors.com/">Wholesale Hair</a></span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-measure-your-wig-length">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>When you <strong>measuring</strong> your hair <strong>wig</strong>, for curly and wavy hair, it should be stretched to straight when you <strong>measure</strong> the hair <strong>length</strong>.</p>
<p>The hair <strong>length</strong> should be from the wig top to the hair end as the hair is straight.</p>
<p>Here below is the correct way to measure a wig, pls check:</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/7D232275-83F8-4be6-AFEE-891AC75911EA_480x480.jpg?v=1609211674" alt=""></p>
<p>Wholesale, Drop Shipping and Customized Hair Package,</p>
<p>Pls feel free to contact:</p>
<p>Tel/Whatsapp: +86 185 8876 9406 , Direct Link to Whatsapp <span><a href="https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406">https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406</a></span></p>
Email: <a href="mailto:luxy1@baisihair.com">luxy1@baisihair.com</a>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-do-i-know-my-wig-cap-size</id>
    <published>2019-12-14T14:46:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:34+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-do-i-know-my-wig-cap-size"/>
    <title>How Do I Know My Wig Cap Size?</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>To <strong>determine</strong> the right <strong>size wig</strong> for you, measuring the circumference of <strong>your</strong> head from the front hairline, behind <strong>your</strong> ear, to the nape of <strong>your</strong> neck, to <strong>your</strong> other ear and then back to the front hairline is necessary.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-do-i-know-my-wig-cap-size">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>To <strong>determine</strong> the right <strong>size wig</strong> for you, measuring the circumference of <strong>your</strong> head from the front hairline, behind <strong>your</strong> ear, to the nape of <strong>your</strong> neck, to <strong>your</strong> other ear and then back to the front hairline is necessary. Pls check the table chart below：</p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/2_9869aaea-4ce7-4a8c-a0a7-cd7eb639d2e2.png?v=1576306008" alt=""></p>
<p>Usually, the Average <strong>Cap wigs</strong> are the most popular <strong>wig size</strong> since they have adjustable straps that give up to a half inch either way for a comfortable &amp; secure fit. Average <strong>Cap Wigs</strong> have a circumference of 22”.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Wholesale, Drop Shipping and Customized Hair Package,</p>
<p>Pls feel free to contact:</p>
<p>Tel/Whatsapp: +86 185 8876 9406 , Direct Link to Whatsapp <span><a href="https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406">https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406</a></span></p>
Email: <a href="mailto:luxy1@baisihair.com">luxy1@baisihair.com</a>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/what-is-hair-density-150-and-200</id>
    <published>2019-12-14T14:41:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:36+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/what-is-hair-density-150-and-200"/>
    <title>What is Hair Density？(150% and 200%)</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Density is defined as how thick or thin the hair on your lace wig will be. <br>The standard density is 150% which is Medium Density. <a style="display: none;" href="https://www.lacefrontwigs.fr/">Perruque</a></span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/what-is-hair-density-150-and-200">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong>Density is</strong> defined as how thick or thin the <strong>hair</strong> on your lace wig <strong>will</strong> be. </p>
<p>The standard <strong>density is 150</strong>% which <strong>is</strong> Medium <strong>Density</strong>. If you <strong>do</strong> not like your <strong>hair</strong> to be too thick we suggest starting out with Light to Medium <strong>Density</strong>.</p>
<p><strong>And 200</strong>% <strong>density</strong> (Natural <strong>Full</strong>) is a nice <strong>density</strong> for ladies who want their <strong>hair</strong> to look natural with full and thick hair.</p>
<p>Here below is the pic of how density shows, pls check:</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/1_cb900ab3-6af9-41ab-845b-98315e445c75.png?v=1576305668" alt=""></p>
<p>Wholesale, Drop Shipping and Customized Hair Package,</p>
<p>Pls feel free to contact:</p>
<p>Tel/Whatsapp: +86 185 8876 9406 , Direct Link to Whatsapp <span><a href="https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406">https://api.whatsapp.com/send?phone=8618588769406</a></span></p>
<p>Email: <span><a href="mailto:luxy1@baisihair.com">luxy1@baisihair.com</a></span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-take-care-of-your-hair</id>
    <published>2019-07-02T11:53:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:40+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-take-care-of-your-hair"/>
    <title>How to Take Care of Your Hair</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><br>Want to keep your Brazilian Hair under the weave healthy and strong. There is no point of wearing a protective style if your refuse to care for your hair. So Hair brings you some methods on care for your real hair.<br><br>Moisturize<br>You are obsessive about keeping your hair moisturized underneath a sew-in Human Hair Weave. Your go to choice of moisturizer is a braid spray. You will use a braid spray or moisturizer generously on the Hair every other day. This takes care of your scalp as well, and it ensures that you won't have dry/brittle hair when you remove the braids.<br><br>Oiling<br>Your scalp can get very dry under a weave and it isn't uncommon for you to experience a few flakes. Oiling your scalp nightly is something you try to do faithfully. Purchasing a bottle with a thin nozzle, or a spray bottle and filling it with your favorite oil will do the trick. Apply this oil liberally to the natural hair only. You don't want to get your sew-in weave greasy as this will ruin the quality <a style="display: none;" href="https://www.wholesaleminkhairvendors.com/">Wholesale Hair</a>.<br><br>Washing<br>The natural hair and weave hair must be washed weekly no matter what. Healthy hair grows out of a clean and healthy scalp. Being in a weave is no excuse to not wash the hair. You are careful to use a sulfate-free shampoo during this time.<br><br>Deep Conditioning<br>After shampooing the hair and weave, you apply a deep conditioner on both the weave hair and your exposed hair and sit under a hooded dryer for at least 30 minutes. The natural hair and weave love this process, and it also helps to keep the hair moist.<br><br>Protect Your Hairline<br>You protect your hairline by massaging castor oil into it every single night and while styling if I remember. Weaves and braids can wreak havoc on the hairline if you are not careful. Take the necessary precaution by massaging and applying castor oil as often as possible. Also, during installation, make sure the braids aren't too taught.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/the-real-meaning-of-valentine-s-day</id>
    <published>2019-02-14T14:00:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:37+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/the-real-meaning-of-valentine-s-day"/>
    <title>The Real Meaning of Valentine’s Day</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Valentine’s Day is a celebration of love and it is an opportunity for us to truly reconnect with the real meaning of this day. It is about LOVE, sharing and giving.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/the-real-meaning-of-valentine-s-day">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Valentine’s Day is a celebration of love and it is an opportunity for us to truly reconnect with the real meaning of this day. It is about LOVE, sharing and giving.</p>
<p>Love is the most amazing thing in our lives. It is what makes us human, what makes life worth living. Nothing else truly matters. The size of our homes, bank balances, the beauty of our partner, the speed of our car – all those things pale into insignificance when we face the splendour of what it is that makes us tick.</p>
<p><em>“Love does not make the world go around – it simply makes the ride worthwhile”.</em></p>
<p><em><span>Love is much greater than what we feel romantically. It is what makes us sing, dance and makes us human.</span></em></p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://www.baisiwig.com/collections/baisi-hair-10a-peruvian-virgin-hair"><span style="text-decoration: underline;">10A Peruvian Virgin Hair</span></a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.baisiwig.com/collections/bob-wig"><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Bob Wig</span></a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-use-coupon-code</id>
    <published>2018-08-18T11:40:00+08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-17T16:45:38+08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-use-coupon-code"/>
    <title>How to use coupon code?</title>
    <author>
      <name>zeyu li</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>When you want buy Baisi hair, do you want have more deals? You can use Baisi hair coupon code to ...</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.baisiwig.com/blogs/news/how-to-use-coupon-code">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>When you want buy Baisi hair, do you want have more deals? You can use Baisi hair coupon code to get more discount, and where can get this coupon code, please check our homepage , you will get Baisi hair coupon code latest.</p>
<h3><span style="color: #ff0000;">1. View the coupon and get the coupon code.</span></h3>
<p><a href="https://www.baisiwig.com/"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/001.png?v=1534562497" alt=""></a></p>
<h3><span style="color: #ff0000;">2. Enter the coupon code.</span></h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/002.png?v=1534563329" alt=""></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1942/4763/files/003.png?v=1534563370" alt=""></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
